so we're in a we're in a battle and that
所以我们在我们在战斗中和
battle is for sexual purity and the
战斗是为了性纯洁和
thing is if you want to maintain sexual
事情是，如果你想保持性
purity
纯度
you must there are things that you and I
你必须有你和我的东西
are responsible to do remember we are
有责任记住我们
doing this not in our own strength but
这样做不是靠我们自己的力量而是
in this strength and the power that the
在这种力量和权力的
Holy Spirit gives us but we are to renew
圣灵赐给我们，但我们要更新
our mind and think God's thoughts after
我们的思想和思考上帝的思想
him so where do we find God's thoughts
他，我们在哪里找到上帝的想法
we find his thoughts in the word and a
我们在单词和a中找到了他的想法
tremendous book that's been given to us
一个已经给了我们巨大的书
in the Old Testaments The Book of
在旧约圣经中
Proverbs and you'll notice in my notes
谚语，你会在我的笔记中注意到
that with apologies to Rick Holland I
向Rick Holland道歉我
first heard him give a message on this
第一次听到他就此发了消息
text and I basically have followed his
文字和我基本上都跟着他
outline as I developed the of this
我开发了这个概述
message basically I did follow his
消息基本上我跟着他
outline and so I'm giving him credit
大纲，所以我给他信任
here as he broke down this text and so
在这里他打破了这个文本等等
the first step is this you're gonna work
第一步是你要工作了
with folks that are dealing with sexual
与被处理性 人
sin you're gonna deal with this in your
你会在你的身上处理这件事
own life and what do you need to do well
自己的生活， 你有什么需要做的很好
you need to undertake the pursuit of
你需要承担起追求
biblical instruction look at Matt and
圣经教导看马特和
look at proverbs and chapter 5 verses 1
看看谚语和第5章第1节
& 2 the notes in the left-hand column of
＆2左侧栏中的注释
your notes my son give attention to my
你的笔记我的儿子注意我的
wisdom incline your ear to my
智慧倾向于我的耳朵
understanding that you may observe
理解你可能会观察到
discretion and your lips may reserve
谨慎和你的嘴唇可以保留
knowledge there's a parallel passage in
知识有一个平行通道中
proverbs chapter 7 if you look at
如果你看一下谚语第7章
proverbs chapter 7 and the beginning of
谚语第7章和开头
chapter 7 it reads this way my son keep
第7章它以我儿子的方式读取
my words treasure my Commandments within
我的话珍惜我的诫命
you keep my Commandments and live and my
你遵守我的诫命，生活和我的
teaching as the apple of your eye bind
作为你眼中的苹果教学
them on your fingers write them on the
他们用手指把它们写在了
tablet of your heart say to wisdom you
你心中的平板电脑对你说智慧
are my sister and call understanding
是我的妹妹和电话谅解
your intimate friend why that day may
亲密的朋友， 为什么那一天可能
keep you from an adulteress from the
让你远离一个淫妇
foreigner or the strange woman who
外国人还是陌生的女人
flatters with her words you see that the
奉承她的话，你看到了
foreigner the strange woman any woman
外国人陌生女人任何一个女人
who isn't the one God has for
谁不是上帝所拥有的
you any man who isn't the man God has
你是不是上帝所拥有的人
for you is the strange woman or the
因为你是陌生的女人或者
strange man for you we are too called
陌生的男人，你我们也被称为
too one flesh one man for one woman for
太一体一个男人对一个女人
life and so as we're called to that we
生活，所以我们被称为我们
leave our father and mother we cleave to
离开我们的父亲和母亲， 我们劈开
our husband or wife we become one flesh
我们的丈夫或妻子，我们成为一体
and we serve God together for his glory
我们为了他的荣耀一起为上帝服务
as we're called to that then any other
因为我们被召唤到那时任何其他人
man or woman is a strange man or woman
男人或女人是一个陌生的男人或女人
to us a foreigner to us and so the idea
给我们一个外国人给我们这样的想法
is the word and the pursuit of the word
是这个词的词和追求
will keep you from that you need to be
会让你远离你需要的
taking the Word of God into your heart
将神的话语带入你的心中
hiding it into your heart give attention
把它藏在心里要注意
to my wisdom incline your ear to my
我的智慧倾向于你的耳朵
understanding that you may observe
理解是 ，您可能会发现
description discretion and that your
描述自由裁量权和你的
lips may reserve knowledge you see it's
嘴唇可以保留你所看到的知识
a dedicated commitment to that look at
对此的专注承诺
what 2nd Timothy 2:22 says in your notes
提摩太后书2:22在你的笔记中说了些什么
now flee from youthful lusts and pursue
现在逃避年轻的欲望和追求
righteousness faith love and peace were
正义的信仰爱与和平是
those who call on the Lord from a pure
那些从纯洁中呼求主的人
heart tomorrow morning we'll be talking
明天早上我们会说话
in detail about the process of difficult
详细讲述了困难的过程
age put off the old man put on the new
年龄推迟了老人穿上了新的
man through the renewing of your mind
男人通过更新你的思想
your mind is your whole inner being it
你的思想是你的整个内心
is your heart your will your emotion
是你的心，你的意志是你的情感
your whole inner being you renew your
你的整个内心是你更新你的
whole inner being
整个内心
how by thinking God's thoughts after him
如何通过思考上帝的思想来追随他
and by asking God thought God to change
并且通过祈求上帝认为上帝改变
your own thinking and bring it in line
你自己的想法，并使其符合要求
with his you ask him to give you the
与他的你问他给你
will and the power to obey his word give
意志和服从他的话语的力量
you the will to do it and give you the
你的意愿去做，给你
power to do it but it comes through the
动力做，但说到通过
understanding of his word and then
理解他的话然后
asking him to complete that work in you
请他完成你的工作
and we'll talk about that process this
我们会谈论这个过程
morning but that's what this verse says
早上，但这就是这节经文所说的
flee from youthful lusts and pursue
逃避年轻的欲望和追求
righteousness faith love and peace with
正义的信念和爱和平
those who call on the Lord from a pure
那些从纯洁中呼求主的人
heart so if you look at the next pages
心脏所以如果你看下面的网页
of you know
你知道吗
and in the middle using second Timothy
而在中间使用第二个提摩太
2:20 to determine your areas of
2:20确定你的领域
respectful distance your flight strategy
尊重你的飞行策略
and and the areas where you need to just
以及你需要的区域
deny yourself entrance to any kind of
否认自己进入任何一种
sense if this is a temptation to you you
感觉如果这是你的诱惑
flee youthful lusts so you don't go to
逃避年轻的私欲， 所以你不去
Walgreens and walk through the magazine
Walgreens 并走过杂志
section when you're walking through the
当你走过的时候
the line going out you don't look to see
走出去的线你看不出来
if they've got Cosmopolitan on the shelf
如果他们有货架上的大都会
because the picture on the front of
因为前面的图片
Cosmopolitan could almost many cases go
丽都几乎可以很多情况下， 去
on the front of Playboy and so you just
在花花公子的前面， 所以你只是
I straight ahead we're going through
我直接前进，我们正在经历
that aisle you got a I mean you know
那个过道你得到了我的意思你知道
STUV us have to go shopping so you're
STUV我们必须去购物，所以你
gonna have to go through the aisle at
会必须在经过过道
Rell's and you know but let's keep our
Rell's ，你知道，但让我们保持
eyes straight ahead let's focus and
直视前方让我们关注焦点
we're gonna flee but then what is my
我们会逃离然后我的是什么
pattern for determining to pursue
决定追求的模式
righteousness faith love and peace and
正义的信念和爱和平，
look at what it says with those who call
看看 那些打电话的人说的话
on the Lord from a pure heart ah who
关于主从一个纯洁的心啊谁
will I be accountable with where will my
我将与问责会在哪里
accountability take place if you look at
如果你看一下问责制就会发生
the next page of your notes page 3 in
笔记3页下页
this section keeping the vessel clean
本节保持船舶清洁
accountability there's a whole pattern
问责制有一个完整的模式
for accountability here you get 1 2 3 4
对于问责制，你得到1 2 3 4
guys probably doesn't work if you have
如果你有的话，伙计们可能不会工作
more than 4 probably 3 is better but the
超过4可能3更好但是
reason is you need a small group and you
原因是你需要一个小团体和你
need ones that you're willing to be
需要你愿意成为的人
honest with and ones that will hold you
诚实的和那些会抱着你的
accountable who will hold your feet to
负起责任的人是谁
the fire to become what God wants you to
火成为上帝要你的东西
be and you've got 13 suggested questions
是的，你有13个建议的问题
here and questions 6 have you been
在这里和问题6你有没有
looking at questionable materials movies
看着有问题的材料电影
TV or books that would bring shame to
电视或书籍会带来耻辱
the Lord would you be willing to tell
你愿意告诉主吗？
the whole congregation what movies you
整个会众是什么电影你
watch this past week if that then
如果是这样那么看过去一周
probably you shouldn't have watched it
可能你不应该看过它
you know another way to word that is
你知道另一种方式来字，它
would you have watched that movie with
你会看过这部电影吗？
Jesus sitting next to you reality Jesus
坐在你旁边的耶稣现实耶稣
was sitting next to you Jesus is living
坐在你旁边耶稣活着
in you in the person of the Holy Spirit
你在圣灵 的人
and so how did you impact your marriage
所以你是如何影响你的婚姻的
and family for the love of Christ this
和家人为基督的爱这个
week what could you do to improve so did
你可以做些什么改进呢？
you pray for your future wife this week
你本周为你未来的妻子祈祷
or did you pray for the wife you have
还是你为你的妻子祈祷？
how are you trying to positively impact
你怎么努力产生积极影响
your family accountability questions in
你的家庭责任问题
other areas of life look at 13 have you
其他生活领域看你有13个
in any way lied or compromised to me
以任何方式欺骗或妥协我
isn't that a fun question you know you
这不是一个你认识的有趣问题
know the last question well as we've
我们知道最后一个问题
talked this morning and we've gone
今天早上说话，我们走了
through our accountability list have you
通过我们的问责清单有你
in any way lied or you know been
以任何方式说谎或你认识了
deceitful in what you've talked about or
欺骗你所谈论的内容或
compromised so you can tell the truth
妥协， 所以你可以说实话
and live at the same time did you know
和你同时住在一起吗？
that I'll come here late for work this
我会迟到这里上班
morning
早上
god I got stuck in traffic boss truth
上帝，我陷入交通老板的真相
you overslept by 45 minutes or you
你迟到了45分钟或者你
wouldn't have been in that traffic jam
不应该在交通堵塞
but you were stuck in the traffic jam so
但你被困在堵车等等
you told the truth and lied at the same
你说的是实话并撒谎
time because the boss wise wants to know
时间因为老板明智想知道
why you were late and the real truth of
为什么你迟到了，真正的真相
why you were late was you punch the
你迟到的原因是你打了一拳
snooze button six times and so you got
打盹按钮六次，所以你得到了
up forty-five minutes late so you told
你告诉我迟到了四十五分钟
the truth and lied at the same time
真相和谎言在同一时间
aren't we amazing people you know I mean
我不是意味着你知道我们的人
when it comes to sinning we're pretty
当谈到犯罪我们很漂亮
amazing yeah but we have an amazing God
太棒了但是我们有一个了不起的神
who gives us hope if you look down to
如果你看不起，谁给了我们希望
the bottom you know the hope that we
在底部，你知道我们的希望
have is we confess our sin you know in
我们是否承认你所知道的罪
that group okay I can admit I sin I
那个团体好吧我可以承认我犯了罪
confess that sin and then I change and I
承认罪，然后我改变和我
put on the light in Christ but you need
在基督里放光， 但你需要
a plan and you're gonna undertake a plan
一个计划，你将采取一个计划
to pursue biblical instruction Matthew 4
追求圣经的指示马太福音4
1 through 11 how does Jesus resist sin
1到11 耶稣如何抵挡罪恶
it is written it is written it is
它是写的它是写的
written he says it is written in the
写的，他说这是写在
first time and then Satan comes in the
第一次，然后撒旦进来了
second time and Satan uses Scripture
第二次和撒旦使用圣经
Satan can use scripture he knows
撒但可以使用他所知道的经文
Scripture and he uses Scripture with you
圣经和他一起使用圣经
know he takes him up to the high place
知道他把他带到了高处
it says you can cast yourself down Bible
它说你可以把自己投下 圣经
says you know he
说你知道他
you you he will keep you from dashing
你，他会让你远离潇洒
your foot against a stone and and Jesus
你的脚对着石头和耶稣
said yeah but it is written
说是的，但它是写的
don't tempt the Lord your God you know
你知道，不要试探耶和华你的神
yes it's written that the angels go
是的，写的是天使去了
before you and this you know aside you
之前你和这个你知道你一边
guys in my church back in buy/sell used
我教会里的家伙买回来卖
to tease me they would say you know Bob
逗我， 他们会说你认识鲍勃
if you would not test the Lord in the
如果你不想在主里试验主
way you drive he could relieve the four
你开车的方式他可以解除四个
angels that he puts on each corner of
他放在每个角落的天使
your card and send them someplace else
你的卡并将它们发送到其他地方
to do work you know now I don't really
做你现在知道的工作我不是真的
think my driving was that bad but you
我认为我的驾驶很糟糕但是你
know that was that's the story that went
知道这就是故事
around that they talked about so you see
他们谈论的是你所看到的
yes angels are there to protect us but
是的天使在那里保护我们但是
we don't tempt the Lord our God we need
我们不要试探我们需要的主我们的上帝
to know all of Scripture so we are to
知道所有的经文，所以我们要这样做
take scripture in its conduct James 4:7
詹姆斯书4：7中的经文
submit therefore to God resist the devil
因此，请上帝抵抗魔鬼
and he will flee from you Romans 13:14
罗马书13:14他会逃避你
you put on here it is put on the Lord
你穿上这里就是戴上了主
Jesus Christ make no provision for the
耶稣基督 作出的 任何规定
lusts of the flesh and I have that
肉体的欲望，我有
script rewrite here for you sorry I
脚本在这里重写对不起我
didn't put it up but Romans 13:14 think
没有提起，但罗马书13:14想
about it again put off put on put on the
关于它再次推迟穿上了
Lord Jesus Christ the put on comes first
主耶稣基督首先出现
what do you think about Jesus if I'm
如果我是你，你怎么看耶稣呢？
thinking about Jesus I won't be
想着耶稣，我不会
undressing that woman in my mind if I'm
如果我的话，在我的脑海里脱掉那个女人
thinking about Jesus what he did for me
想着耶稣他为我做了什么
on the cross then I will not be lusting
在十字架上然后我不会好色
after that other situation and then what
在那之后的其他情况然后是什么
do you do make no provision do not make
你做不做任何规定吗？
any allowance for that just don't go
任何津贴只是不去
there here's the site it pops up I
这里是我弹出 的网站
didn't have anything to do with it you
没跟你有任何关系
know I was sitting in my office one day
我知道有一天我会坐在办公室里
and visalia and I hear from the next
和visalia，我听到了下一个
office no no oh my oh no oh what oh man
办公室不，没有哦，我的哦，不，哦，哦，男人
what am I gonna do what's going on in
我将要做什么在做什么
there I run around the corner and at
在那里， 我跑到拐角处
this point Chuck's computer is
这一点Chuck的电脑是
completely blank
完全空白
what's the matter Chuck so not alone
怎么回事Chuck并不孤单
he's
他是
it popped up on my screen he was doing
它突然出现在我正在做的屏幕上
an internet search for something and he
互联网搜索的东西和他
said and it was bad and he said I hit
说，这很糟糕，他说我打了
the exit and it got worse and I hit it
出口，它变得更糟，我打了它
again and it got worse again so I just
再次，它再次变得更糟，所以我只是
hit the power button and held it down
按下电源按钮并按住它
until the whole thing went children you
直到整个事情都是你的孩子
know he's sitting in the church office
知道他坐在教堂办公室
you know his computer faces the wall the
你知道他的电脑面向墙壁
doors open you know you're not gonna be
门打开，你知道你不会是
messing around in that situation but you
在那种情况下搞乱，但你
know that's there and that thing happens
知道那就在那里，那件事发生了
what do you do whole flee you know hit
你做什么整个逃跑，你知道命中
the power button and kill the thing you
电源按钮并杀死你的东西
know that's when we finally you know got
知道那是我们终于知道的时候了
a covenant eyes type of thing on our
事情在契约眼睛类型我们
computers at the office and began to
在办公室的电脑，并开始
realize you got a you got the guard
意识到你有你得到了后卫
every way you can in these situations
在这些情况下你可以采取各种方式
and so you make no provision for the
所以你没有为此做出任何规定
flesh in regards to its lust don't give
关于其欲望的 肉体 不给予
the flesh an inch because it'll take a
肉体一英寸，因为它需要一个
mile
英里
you need accountability as we talked
在谈话时你需要问责制
about it there all right and then well
关于它那么好，然后很好
what's the next step understand the
什么是下一步了解的
deception of sexual sin look at proverbs
欺骗性罪看谚语
chapter 5 verses 3 to 6 for the lips of
第5章第3至6节的嘴唇
an adulteress drip honey and smoother
一个淫妇滴蜂蜜和更顺畅
than oil as her speech but in the end
而不是石油作为她的演讲，但最终
she is a bitter as wormwood sharp as a
她像艾草一样苦涩
two-edged sword her feet go down to
双刃剑， 她的双脚往下走
death her steps take hold of Sheol she
死了她的脚步抓住Sheol她
does not ponder the path of life her
不思考她的生活之路
ways are unstable she does not know it
方式不稳定， 她不知道
you've got to understand the deception
你必须了解这种欺骗行为
of sexual sin you know if you turn to
如果你转向，你知道性罪
proverbs chapter 7 and you look at
谚语第7章，你看看
verses 6 through 23 that's a commentary
第6至23节这是一篇评论
on this passage and if you look there
在这段经文上，如果你看那里
you see you know the the man is standing
你看，你知道那个男人正站着
at the window of his house and he's
在他家的窗户和他的
looking out through his Latisse and he
通过他的Latisse和他看
sees among the naive that is the the
看到了天真就是那个
unknowing ones I discerned among the
不知不觉的我在其中看到了
youth a young man who lacks sense and
青春的年轻人谁没有意识，
he's passing through the street near her
他正经过她附近的街道
corner see he's not obeying what he
角落看他不服从他
should have learned don't make any
应该学会不做任何
provision
规定
don't go down that Street you know if
不要走那条你知道的街道
that's a motel that's known for an
这是一个专门针对一个已知的汽车旅馆
hourly rate don't stay there if you are
小时费率不要留在那里，如果你
tempted because you have to go on a
诱惑， 因为你必须继续
business trip you asked three men to
出差你问三个男人
hold you accountable you asked them at
让你负责，你问他们
the desk to disable the television
桌子禁用电视
before you get there or you just make
在你到达那里之前或者你刚刚完成
yourself accountable three men you're
你自己负责三个男人
not even gonna watch TV because they
甚至都不会看电视， 因为他们
have the HBO and that kind of stuff that
有HBO和那样的东西，
you normally don't have access to so you
你通常没有获得，所以你
make no provision for the flesh the
不要为肉体没有规定的
senseless young man he goes down that
他毫无意义的年轻人
street he takes the way to her house and
街道他走到她的房子和
in the Twilight and in the evening in
在暮光之城和傍晚
the middle of the night in the darkness
在黑暗中的深夜
behold a woman comes to meet him she's
看到一个女人来见她
dressed seductively as a harlot and
诱人地穿着妓女和
cunning of heart
狡猾的心
she's boisterous and rebellious her feet
她的脚很喧闹而叛逆
do not remain at home she's now in the
不要留在家里，她现在在家里
streets and now in the squares and lurks
街道，现在在广场和潜伏
by every corner she seizes him and
在每个角落，她都抓住了他
kisses him and with a brazen face she
亲吻他，脸上带着厚颜无耻的她
says to him I was due to offer peace
对他说， 我应该提供和平
offerings that I was in church this
我在教堂里的礼物
morning I've paid my vows you know I
早上我付出了我的誓言，你知道我
gave in the offering
奉献给了
I made a sacrifice and now I've come to
我做了一个牺牲，现在我来了
meet you really just me not really
见到你真的只是我不是真的
but she's seductive she's deceptive she
但她很诱人，她欺骗她
makes you think you are a special one
让你觉得你是一个特别的人
when indeed that's not the case at all
确实情况确实如此
to seek your presence earnestly and I
我真诚地 寻求你的存在
have found you and I've spread my couch
找到了你，我已经铺开了沙发
with coverings and colored linens of
有遮盖物和彩色床单
Egypt sprinkled my bed with myrrh and
埃及在我的床上洒了没药和
aloes you know it's Corral number five
aloes你知道它是Corral五号
and with myrrh and cinnamon come let us
让没药和肉桂来吧
drink our fill of love until morning
直到早上喝我们的爱
let's delight ourselves with caresses
让我们用爱抚来取悦自己
for the man is not at home we won't get
对于男人不在家 ，我们不会得到
caught he's gone on a long journey
抓住他走了很长一段路
taking a bag of money with him full moon
和他满月一袋钱
he'll come home with many persuasions
他会带着许多说服回家
she entices him with her flattering lips
她用她讨人喜欢的嘴唇诱惑着他
she just seduces him suddenly he follows
她突然引诱他，他紧随其后
her like an ox going to the slaughter or
她像牛一样去屠宰或者屠宰
his one in fetters to the discipline of
他在一个羁绊的纪律
a fool until an arrow pierces through
一个傻瓜直到箭刺穿
his liver as a bird Hey
他的肝脏像鸟一样嘿
to the snare he does not know that it
对陷阱他不知道
will cost him his life
将耗费他的生命
here's a commentary on the passage in
这里的通道在一篇评论
proverbs 5 you got to begin to
谚语5你得开始
understand the deception she'll tell you
了解她会告诉你的欺骗行为
that you're the only one but you aren't
你是唯一一个，但你不是
if she's doing this with you she'll do
如果她和你一起这样做，她会这么做的
it with somebody else you know they make
它与你知道他们做的其他人
it look so good you know those pictures
它看起来很好，你知道那些照片
are airbrushed they are touched up in
被喷刷他们在感动了
every way and nobody looks that good I
各方面， 没有人看起来那么好我
mean just face it nobody looks that good
意思是面对它没有人看起来那么好
you know I mean it just doesn't happen
你知道我的意思是它不会发生
in life I mean we've got bifocals or
在生活中， 我的意思是我们有双焦点或者
trifocals or you know whatever you're
trifocals或你知道你是什​​么
all catching up to me and you know it
一切都赶上了我， 你知道
doesn't get better it gets worse and you
变得越来越好，你变得更糟
got to understand there's a deception in
必须明白有一个在欺骗
sexual sin how do you contact that read
性罪你怎么联系那读
the book of Proverbs read it every month
箴言书每个月都会读它
that way you read proverbs 5 at proverbs
这样你就会在谚语中读到谚语5
6 and proverbs 7 in Proverbs 9 and you
6 和箴言9中的箴言7和你
will have it reinforced over and over
会一遍又一遍地加强它
again so that when you're in the
再次，这样当你在
elevator and the lady says as you say
电梯和那位女士如你所说
well what button what floor are you
那是什么按钮你是什么楼层
going to because you're you know you
去，因为你是认识你的
just push the button for your floor and
只需轻轻一按 您的地板，
and she says well what floor are you
她说你在哪个楼层
going to and you say 1 7 and she said
去，然后你说1 7，她说
well that'll do well then you know
那么你会知道的那么好
you're in trouble ok
你遇到了麻烦
and the pastor that told me this story
以及告诉我这个故事的牧师
said you know the first thing I thought
说你知道我想的第一件事
about was not you know my loving wife
你不知道我爱的妻子吗？
the first thing you thought might see it
你认为第一件事可能会看到它
was fear of God I play with this and my
害怕上帝我和这个以及我一起玩
whole ministry is over and it was the
整个事工已经结束了
fear of God but part of that was his
敬畏上帝， 但其中一部分是他的
reading in Proverbs you know this is the
在箴言中读到你知道这就是
way to the slaughterhouse this is the
这是屠宰场的方式
way to the end of life I'm not going
生命结束的方式我不会去
there and so we have to make decision
在那里我们必须做出决定
understand the value then of a safe
了解保险箱的价值
distance 2nd Timothy 2:22
距离提摩太后书2:22
we looked at now flee from youthful lust
我们现在看着逃离年轻的欲望
and pursue righteousness faith love and
追求正义的信仰爱情
peace with those who call on the Lord
与那些呼求主的人和平相处
but you flee first you know no the
但你首先逃跑，你知道没有
Joseph printable know when to punt or
约瑟夫打印知道何时平底船或
you know make this quote you know
你知道这个引用你知道吗
remember if you don't remember anything
记住，如果你不记得任何东西
else for the run remember this
其他的运行记得这个
run baby run okay you know know when to
跑宝贝跑好你知道什么时候去
run make no provision flee Genesis 39
没有任何条款逃离创世纪39
get out of there Joseph she grabbed him
走出约瑟夫，她抓住了他
by the cold you can have the coat but
在寒冷的时候你可以穿上大衣但是
you can't have me and he's out of there
你不能拥有我，他离开那里
a consequences to that she lied about
一个后果，她谎报
him and he ended up in prison but he
他和他最终入狱，但他
didn't end up sinning against God
最终没有犯罪反对上帝
sinning against her and sinning against
对她犯罪并且犯罪
his master and God was still at work now
他的主人和上帝 现在还在工作
taking him to the prison where he would
带他去监狱
meet the guys who would eventually put
遇见最终会放弃的人
him in contact with the Pharaoh and so
他与法老等有联系
understand the value of a safe distance
了解安全距离的价值
there is an account about a man a very
有一个关于男人的帐户
wealthy man who intended to hire his
打算雇用他的富人
next chauffeur and so as each chauffeur
下一位司机以及每位司机
would come to apply he took them on a
他会接受他们的申请
particular mountain road and on the
特别是山路上
mountain road he got out of the car with
山路上，他下了车用
a very precarious curve and he said now
一条非常不稳定的曲线，他现在说
I want you to take the car around that
我想让你看看周围的车
corner and I want you to get as close to
角落，我希望你尽可能接近
the edge as you can and still be safe
尽可能的边缘，仍然是安全的
first guy came within about two feet of
第一个人来到了大约两英尺之内
the edge he said no thank you to the man
他说，没有边缘谢谢你的男人
second guy got within a foot no thank
第二个家伙在一英尺内没有感谢
you to the man
你对那个男人
third guy got within six inches said no
第三个家伙在6英寸内说没有
thank you to the man fourth guy got
谢谢那个男人第四个得到了
basically in the middle of the road so
基本上在路中间所以
that he was safe being able to watch
他能安全地观看
what would be coming around and as far
这将是未来的四周，就
away from the edge as he could be to go
远离边缘，因为他可能会去
around the corner he hired him see he
在他附近他雇用他看他
wasn't looking for somebody who would to
不是在寻找有人愿意的人
prove his skill get as close to that
证明他的技能接近于此
edge and possibly lose him in his car he
边缘，可能会把他丢进他的车里
was looking for the person who knew
正在寻找知道的人
the the quality of a safe distance so
这样安全距离的质量
you got to know the principle here of
你必须知道这里的原理
what is safe distance and then the
什么是安全距离，然后是
fourth principle is this you unmask the
第四个原则是你解开这个
regret unmasked the regret of the
后悔揭露的遗憾
consequences of sin think about it think
罪的后果考虑它思考
of the testimony of Solomon in
所罗门的见证
Deuteronomy 1717 the Word of God is very
申命记1717上帝的话是非常的
clear it says that the kings of Israel
明确表示以色列的国王
are not to multiply for themselves wise
不要为自己明智地增加
from foreign countries so they're not to
来自国外， 所以他们不这样做
multiply foreign wise okay now think of
现在想到的是外国智慧的好处
Solomon's disobedience and let me read
所罗门不服从，让我读
to you from first Kings 11 one through
从第一次国王11到你
four and following and listen to this
四，并听取这个
you see who was the wisest man that ever
你看到谁是最聪明的人是有史以来
lived
生活
Solomon good you're still awake alright
所罗门好，你还是醒着还好吧
that's it that's a good sign and why is
那是一个好兆头，为什么呢
this man that ever lived but he wasn't
这个曾经生活过的人， 但他不是
smart enough to get away with this sin
足够聪明，可以逃脱这种罪恶
Deuteronomy 17 don't multiply wise what
申命记17不会成倍增加
is Solomon do he multiplies wise King
是所罗门他是否倍增智慧国王
Solomon I love many foreign women along
所罗门我爱很多外国女人
with the daughter of Pharaoh on a
与法老的女儿在一起
Moabite ammonite Edomites I don't even
Moabite ammonite Edomites我甚至没有
Hittite women from the nation's
来自全国的赫梯女性
concerning which the Lord said to the
关于耶和华所说的
sons of Israel you shall not associate
以色列的儿子，你们不应该联想
with them neither shall they associate
与他们同在， 他们也不会联想
with you for they will surely turn your
和你在一起他们肯定会转过你的
heart away after their God Solomon held
他们的上帝所罗门举行之后心碎了
fast to these in love three hundred
快爱这三个人
wives seven hundred concubines those are
妻子七百妾那些
the other way around
另一种方式
anyways a thousand of them he had seven
无论如何，他有七千人
hundred oh it's right here and then text
一百个哦，它就在这里，然后发短信
verse three seven hundred wise and
三节七百智慧
princes and 300 concubines and his wives
王子和300嫔妃和他的妻子
turned his heart away for it came about
它因此而转过身去
when Solomon was old his wives turned
当所罗门老了，他的妻子转过身来
his heart away after other gods and his
他的心脏远离了其他的神和他的
heart was not wholly devoted to the Lord
心并不是完全献身于主
his God as the heart of David his father
他的上帝是他父亲大卫的心
had been for Solomon went after
曾经为所罗门追求过
Ashtaroth the goddess of the sidonians
西顿人的女神阿斯塔罗斯
and after milcom the untestable god of
并且在milcom之后是不可饶恕的神
the ammonite solomon did what was evil
菊石所罗门做了邪恶的事
in the sight of the lord and did not
在主的视线中，没有
follow the Lord fully as David his
像大卫一样完全跟从主
father's done then Solomon built a high
父亲完成然后所罗门建立了一个高
place for chemists
化学家的地方
detestable I love Moya on the mountain
我讨厌山上的莫亚
which is east of Jerusalem and Ramallah
这是耶路撒冷和拉马拉以东
the detestable Idol of the sons of Haman
哈曼之子的可憎偶像
you know how you worship the Moloch
你知道你如何崇拜莫洛克
you built this altar with arms like this
你建造了这座坛， 像这样的武器
and then you rolled children down that
然后你把孩子们推倒了
into the belly of this Idol that which
进入这个偶像 的肚子 里面
was on fire and you sacrifice children
被点燃， 你牺牲了孩子们
Solomon the wisest man that ever lived
所罗门是有史以来最聪明的人
could not get away with this sin you
无法摆脱这种罪恶你
need to unmask the regret that is there
需要揭露的遗憾是存在的
and the consequences of this kind of sin
以及这种罪恶的后果
and you need to realize you cannot get
而你需要意识到你无法得到
away with this I can't get away with it
离开这个我无法逃脱它
nobody gets away with it there are
有人没有人逃脱它
unbelievable serious consequences look
令人难以置信的严重后果
at what 9 to 14 says you will give your
在9到14岁时你会说你会给你的
vigor to others is that talking about
活力别人是在谈论
STDs and your years to the cruel ones
性病和你的岁月给残忍的人
strangers will be filled with your
陌生人将充满你的
strength your hard-earned Goods will go
你的辛苦赚来的商品将会增加
to the house of an alien and you groan
到外星人的房子，你呻吟
at your final in when your flesh and
在你最后的时候你的肉体和
your body are consumed and you say how
你的身体被消耗了，你说怎么样
have I hated instruction I didn't listen
我讨厌指令我不听
and my heart spurn reproof I have not
我的心脏辱骂我没有
listened to the voice of my teachers I
听了老师的声音我
didn't incline my ear to my instructors
并没有把我的耳朵倾向我的导师
I was almost another ruin in the midst
我几乎是在中间的另一个废墟
of the Assembly of the congregation and
会众大会和
so ruin is coming in this area in
所以废墟即将来到这个地区
Ecclesiastes 7:20 to 7 to 29 Solomon
传道书7:20 至7至29所罗门
says in that book you know one man among
在那本书中你会认识一个人
a thousand I could find but not one in a
我找到了一千个而不是一个
thousand see the only way to do it is
千年看到这样做 是唯一的出路
you seek one one man for one woman you
你为一个女人寻找一个男人
seek one and you're faithful to her you
寻求一个， 你忠实于她
seek one man you're faithful to him then
寻求一个男人你是忠实于他呢
you find it
你找到它
Solomon couldn't find it in two thousand
所罗门在两千人中找不到它
unlock the satisfaction of marital
解开婚姻的满足感
fidelity proverbs 5 15 to 19 look at
忠诚箴言5 15至19看
what it says drink water from your own
它说的是从你自己喝水
cistern fresh water from your own well
从你自己的井里蓄水池淡水
should your Springs be dispersed abroad
如果你的泉水分散在国外
streams of water in the streets
街上的水流
let them be yours alone and not for
让他们独自一人而不是你的
strangers with you let your fountain be
与你同在的陌生人让你的喷泉成为
blessed rejoice in the wife of your
祝福你的妻子，感到高兴
youth and as a loving hind and a
青春，作为一个充满爱心的后躯和一个
graceful doe let her breasts satisfy you
优雅的母鹿让她的乳房让你满意
at all
一点都不
all times be exhilarated always with her
所有的时间总是和她一起兴奋
love and men are attracted by breasts I
爱和男人被乳房吸引我
don't know why God designed it that way
不知道为什么上帝设计的这种方式
but he did and it's right and it's holy
但他做到了，这是正确的，这是圣洁的
in Hebrews it says in chapter 13 the
在希伯来它说，在第13章
marriage bed is a holy place but what
婚床是一个神圣的地方，但是什么
that tells you is pornography is wrong
这告诉你色情是错误的
because it's attracting you to every
因为它吸引着你
other woman's breasts and her body
其他女人的乳房和她的身体
rather than your wife's body you need to
而不是你需要的妻子的身体
write in the notes a parallel passage in
在笔记中写下一条平行的段落
1st Corinthians chapter 7 and verses 1
第一科林斯章7和1节
to 5 Paul talks there about love he does
保罗在那里谈到他所做的爱
it somewhat unromantic ly you have to
它有点平淡LY你必须
apologize for Paul sometimes not really
为保罗道歉有时不是真的
I could get them big trouble here so but
我可以在这里遇到大麻烦但是
it's interesting how he does this not
有趣的是， 他不是这样做的
concerning the things about which you
关于你的事情
wrote it's good for a man not to touch a
写这是很好的一个人不碰
woman weird there is to touch her in
女人很奇怪有触摸她的
such a way as to stimulate her sexually
这样的方式来刺激她的性欲
but because of immorality each man is to
但是因为每个男人都是不道德的
have his own wife and each woman is to
拥有自己的妻子和每个女人都是
have her own husband look there's a lot
让她自己的丈夫看起来很多
of sin going on out there
罪恶在那里发生
so get your own wife get your own
让你自己的妻子得到你自己的
husband Paul doesn't sound real romantic
丈夫保罗听起来并不真实浪漫
I mean no I don't like that the husband
我的意思是不，我不喜欢那个丈夫
must fulfill his duty to his wife
必须履行对妻子的责任
likewise also the wife to her husband
同样也是她丈夫的妻子
okay honey I guess if you want to make
好吧亲爱的我想如果你想做
love I'll have to do it okay I got to
爱我必须这样做我没事
fulfill my duty the wife does not have
履行我妻子没有的职责
authority over her own body but the
权威她自己的身体，但
husband does and likewise also the
老公呢，同样也
husband does not have authority over his
丈夫对他没有权力
own body the wife does stop depriving
自己的身体，妻子确实停止剥夺
one another except by agreement for a
除了通过协议之外，彼此相互关联
time so that you may devote yourselves
时间，以便你可以投入自己
to prayer come together again so that
祈祷再次聚集在一起
Satan will not tempt you because of your
撒旦不会诱惑你，因为 你的
lack of self-control doesn't sound real
缺乏自我控制 听起来并不真实
romantic but there is a nugget of truth
浪漫，但有一个真理的金块
in this text that you do not want to
在这篇文章中你不想这样做
miss it is more blessed to give than it
想念它比给它更有福
is to receive what is the secret of
要接收什么是成功的秘诀
unlocking marital love satisfaction in
释放婚姻中的爱情满足感
the bedroom your body is given to you
卧室是你的身体给你的
to satisfy your wife fear the lady your
为了满足你的妻子害怕女士你的
body has been given to you as a gift to
身体已经作为礼物送给你了
give to your husband that's why you
告诉你的丈夫，这就是你的原因
don't give the gift to anybody else and
不要把礼物送给别人和
when you give that gift that's when real
当你送出真正的礼物时
satisfaction comes in to that marriage
对婚姻的满足感
listen to the story of John and Maria
听听约翰和玛丽亚的故事
not their real names but John and Maria
不是他们的真名， 而是约翰和玛丽亚
came for counseling and things were not
来咨询，事情没有
going well that's why they came for
顺利，这就是为什么他们来的原因
counseling and they walked in what's the
咨询，他们走进了什么
issue well I just don't have any
问题好我只是没有
feelings for her anymore well what do
对她的感情好了做什么
you mean I said I mean just that I don't
你的意思是我说我的意思是我没有
have any feelings for her anymore
对她有任何感情了
but I know that's wrong and I know I'm
但我知道这是错的，我知道我是
supposed to have feelings for her and I
应该 对她和我 有感情
know I'm supposed to love her as Christ
知道我应该爱她作为基督
loved the church and I'm supposed to
喜欢教会，我应该这样做
give myself to hurt but I don't have any
让自己受伤，但我没有
feelings for her anymore well what about
对她的感情已经很好了
you Maria oh she said quote I'm a
你玛丽亚哦，她说我是一个
red-blooded Italian and I have lots of
红血的意大利人和我有很多
feeling for him and I want to be close
对他的感觉，我想要亲近
to him I don't know what's the matter
对他来说我不知道是怎么回事
with him right now but I haven't lost
与他， 但现在我还没有失去
any of my feelings for him so we found
我对他的任何感受， 所以我们找到了
out what's going on well he's working
发生了什么事以及他的工作
about 80 hours a week because he decided
因为他决定，每周大约80个小时
to start his own business and you know
开始自己的事业，你知道
he's actually not going to church he's
他实际上不会去教堂
not doing anything except getting up
除了起床，什么都不做
going to work and be in there longer
上班，再呆在那儿
than he should and coming home trying to
不是他应该和回家尝试
get a few hours sleep and going back to
睡几个小时然后回去
work again
再次工作
he has lost feeling for everything
他已经失去了对一切的感觉
actually so now we went through this
实际上现在我们经历了这个
text because she has said I have a
文字， 因为她说我有一个
strong desire for him I need to be close
对他的强烈渴望我需要亲近
to him I miss him he is that I've lost
对他来说，我想念他，他就是我失败了
all these feelings and so we went
所有这些感受，所以我们去了
through responsibilities that he had he
通过他拥有的责任
needed to get back to a quiet time with
需要回到安静的时间
God he needed to get back to worshiping
上帝他需要回到崇拜
God he needed to get back to leading his
上帝他需要回到领导他的
children now also there are young
孩子现在也有年轻人
married couple they won't have been
已婚夫妇他们不会
married five years they've got three
结婚五年， 他们有三个
kids under five so that's enough to tire
五岁以下的孩子，这足以让人厌倦
you out I mean from a wife's perspective
你是我的意思从妻子的角度来看
as well as the husband because when he
还有丈夫，因为当他
comes home it's not exactly all that
回到家里并不完全是这样
peaceful either and so I give them an
和平，所以我给他们一个
assignment you know you're gonna get
任务，你知道你会得到
back to church you're gonna get back to
回到教堂，你会回来的
your relationship with God you're gonna
你将与​​上帝建立关系
spend five minutes
花五分钟
at least a day praying together and
至少有一天一起祈祷
reading the word together and then he
一起读这个词然后他
said I said and and this week you're
说我说，本周你就是
gonna make love three times he looked at
他会看三次做爱
me and goes said you're crazy
我和你说你疯了
I thought to myself no I'm not crazy you
我心想，不，我不是疯了你
came for counseling you're crazy I'm I'm
来咨询你疯了我是我
the same one here but you know you don't
这里是同一个，但你知道你没有
always say what comes to your mind right
总是说什么涉及到你的头脑权
you think before you speak
你在发言之前想到的
I said wait a minute this isn't my
我说等一下这不是我的
direction this is Paul let's read again
方向这是保罗让我们再读一遍
Matthew seven one two five because we
马太七一二五因为我们
had taken time to go through this test I
我花了很多时间来完成这个测试
had already asked him the question did
他已经问过他这个问题了
you stop making love in order to fast
你为了禁食而 停止做爱
and pray look he said of course no I'm
祈祷看他 当然不是我说的
just lost feeling I've lost desire for
只是失去了我对失去欲望的感觉
her and I said this is what the text
她和我说这就是文字
says your body is not your own it's been
说你的身体不是你自己的身体
given to you to please your wife and I
给你取悦你的妻子和我
said I'm not assigning you Paul is
我说保罗不是你
assigning it to you God is assigning it
把它分配给你上帝正在分配它
to you you have no right to deprive your
对你来说，你没有权利剥夺你的权利
wife in this area you need to minister
你需要在这个地区的妻子服事
to her you need to give her this gift
对她来说， 你需要给她这份礼物
but you can't assign me to make love I
但你不能指派我做爱我
said I'm not God is now I said do you
说我不是上帝现在我说你做
know what pleases her he said well yeah
知道什么让她高兴，他说得很好
of course I do
我当然是了
and then are you willing and he said I
然后你愿意，他说我
don't know this sounds crazy but okay
不知道这听起来很疯狂但没关系
and so I went home they came back and we
所以我就回家了，他们回来了，我们
went through the other aspects of the
经历了其他方面
homework I said all right did you make
做作业我说好了你做的
love three times this week oh I've got
本周爱三次哦，我有
to back up I emphasize to him that
备份我强调地告诉他，
possibly this will be the first time
可能这将是第一次
that you have ever made love for the
你曾经爱过这个
right reason he said what do you mean
正确的理由他说出你的意思
I said well have you ever initiated and
我说你有没有发起过
made love just because you thought Maria
因为你认为玛丽亚而做爱
wanted it and he thought he said I don't
想要它，他认为他说我没有
think so
这么认为
why have you made love he said because
为什么你做了爱，他说，因为
I've had feelings for her and I've
我对她有感情，我也有
desired her and I've wanted to be with
渴望她，我想和她在一起
her and that's always been my basic
她和那一直都是我的基础
motivation so well maybe this week
本周可能也很好
you're gonna make love for the right
你会为正义而做爱
reason
原因
for the first time because you're just
这是第一次，因为你只是
gonna do it to please her that's what I
要做到这一点，以讨好她，这就是我
emphasize do you know what pleases her
强调你知道她喜欢什么
he said yeah came back next week that's
他说是啊回来下周这
what he said
他说的话
when I asked him the question did you
当我问他这个问题做了你
make love this week he said yes once for
本周做爱他曾说过一次
the assignment and twice for the fun of
任务和两次的乐趣
it I say what do you mean he said well
我说你说他说的很好
just like you said okay I knew what
就像你说的好，我知道什么
pleases her I know it has to do with you
拜托她，我知道它与你有关
know you start being affectionate all
知道你开始被所有的深情
the time not just at that time and you
时间不只是在那个时候，你
set the stage and she likes music and
设置舞台， 她喜欢音乐和
she likes quietness and so on and so I
她喜欢安静等等，所以我
said all that and then I I know what
说了这么多，然后II知道是什么
pleases her physically and what she
她的身体和她的喜悦
enjoys and and I just asked God to help
喜欢和我只是求上帝帮助
me do that and he said making love that
我这样做，他说要做爱
night was more satisfying to me than
晚上比我更满意
it's ever been and yet I was doing it
它曾经是，但我在做它
for her and that's unlocking the
对她来说，这是解锁的
satisfaction of marital fidelity and
婚姻忠诚的满意度和
then you want to do this unleash the
然后你想要这样做释放出来
horror of God's omniscience you know
你知道上帝无所不知的恐怖
remember the accountability question
记住问责制问题
there god it's it's never too young
在那里，它永远不会太年轻
people alone in the back seat of a car
独自一人在一辆汽车的后座上的人
or too young people who are alone at the
或者太年轻的人谁是独自在
movies in a sense to other people around
电影在某种意义上对周围的其他人
you but nobody knows us or to people
你但没有人知道我们或人
young people that are alone in the
独自一人的年轻人
bedroom and if you're the parent they
卧室，如果你是他们的父母
shouldn't be in the bedroom alone
不应该单独在卧室里
anyways because that should be
无论如何， 因为那应该是
off-limits but you know you know parents
禁区，但你知道你认识父母
are out later than expected and they got
比预期晚了，他们得到了
home and now they're home alone you know
家里，现在他们就在家了， 你知道
no it it's never that anyways because
不，它永远不会那样，因为
the eyes of the Lord run to and fro
耶和华的眼睛来回奔跑
throughout the earth to show himself
在整个地球上展示自己
strong on behalf of those whose hearts
强烈代表那些心中的人
are purely his second chronicles 16:9
纯粹是他的第二次编年史16：9
and proverbs 15:3 says the eyes of the
和箴言15：3说的是眼睛
Lord run to and fro you know just
上帝来回奔波你知道
observing the evil and the good teacher
观察邪恶和好老师
children from the age of two when your
孩子从两岁开始的时候
disciple as you sit down with them and
弟子当你坐下来与他们
you talk to them about what you caught
你跟他们谈你抓什么
them doing you know proverbs 3 says
他们做你知道谚语说：3
God's eyes are always looking and they
上帝的眼睛总是在寻找他们
behold the evil and they behold
看见邪恶，他们看到了
when you do wrong he sees when you do
当你做错了，他会在你做的时候看到
good he sees and he says that's good and
他看到的很好，他说这很好
teach them that from the time they're
从他们那里开始教他们
beginning with them but in terms of this
从他们开始，但就此而言
I didn't touch on let's go back for just
我没有碰，让我们去回，仅仅为了
a second but in this process recognize
第二个，但在这个过程中认识到
in Psalm 84 11 that gods and the the
在诗篇84 11中，神与神
Lord is our son and his shield he gives
主是我们的儿子和他给他的盾牌
grace and glory
恩典和荣耀
no good thing to see withhold from those
没有好东西，看看那些隐瞒
who walk uprightly and in that proverbs
谁走得很正直，在那个谚语中
19 14 a prudent wife as a gift from God
19 14谨慎的妻子作为上帝的礼物
and in proverbs 18:22 a good wife is
在箴言18:22中， 一个好妻子就是
again a gift from God and then Luke 9:23
再一次是上帝的礼物，然后是路加福音9:23
2:24 serve God first so when you give
2:24首先侍奉上帝，所以当你付出时
yourself to God and then you give your
你自己上帝，然后你给你
body to him for the sake of the gospel
为了福音，身体对他而言
then in part of that whatever you do
然后在你做的任何事情的一部分
whether you eat or drink or whatever you
不管你吃或喝，或任何你
do make love when you make love with
当你爱的时候做爱
your wife you give her the gift of your
你的妻子，你给她的礼物
body and that is rewarding and then
身体， 这是有益的，然后
second Corinthians or first Corinthians
哥林多前书或哥林多前书
7 and those passages talks about
7和那些段落谈论
wherever you are if you're married to an
无论你在哪里，如果你嫁给了一个
unchristian non-christian you give God
非基督徒非基督徒你给上帝
the glory there and you serve so that
荣耀那里，你服务，使
God will be witness to if you're married
如果你结婚了，上帝就会见证
to a godly man you serve Him there if
对于一个敬虔的人，如果你在那里为他服务
you're single you serve in there so as
你是单身， 你在那里服务
you serve God as a single person God
你作为一个单独的上帝侍奉上帝
will bring you to that person he has for
会带你到他所拥有的那个人
you or bring them to you how does a girl
你还是把它们带给你的女孩怎么样？
from Shafter California meet a guy from
来自加利福尼亚州的Shafter遇到一个人
Romulus New York in Chicago both seeking
芝加哥的罗慕路斯纽约都在寻求
God's will and he puts us together there
上帝的旨意和他把我们聚集在一起
and now we've been together for 42 years
现在我们已经在一起42年了
and remembering that you know 1st
并记住你知道第一
Corinthians 10:13 but unleashing the
哥林多前书10:13但释放了
horror of God's omniscience look over at
上帝无所不知的恐怖看着
the last page a couple of pages of your
最后几页你的几页
notes in terms of the repercussions if I
如果我的话会引起反响
give in to lust we don't have time to go
情欲屈服，我们没有时间去
through them you read through them but
通过他们你读过他们但是
under God my name would be added to the
上帝在我的名字将被添加到
long list of Christian leaders who have
有很多基督徒领袖的名单
failed clear down under the woman you
在你的女人身​​下失败了
know my wife will be hurt
知道我的妻子会受伤
spiritually and emotionally her view of
精神上和情感上她的观点
Christ I mean the woman you sin against
基督我是指你犯罪的女人
the her view of Christ will be
她对基督的看法将是
diminished think about your go back
想想你的回归会减少
under the whyte she'll have a hard time
在这个为什么，她会很难过
read
读
building trust she'll have a hard time
建立信任她会很难过
letting me touch her she will have a
让我碰她，她会有一个
harder time touching me all those
更难以触动我所有这些
consequences look under the idea of
后果看下的想法
fellow elders on the next page you will
你将会在下一页的长老们
have disqualified yourself for
已经取消了自己的资格
leadership you'll have to remove
领导你必须删除
yourself from leadership you will have
你将从领导中获得自己
hurt those that have worked with you and
伤害那些与你的工作和
didn't question your character you will
你不会质疑你的角色
disgrace Christ in his church with
在他的教会里羞辱基督
regards to fellow workers at the place
对这个地方的同事们表示敬意
where you work you have put yourself up
你在哪里工作，你已经把自己搞砸了
as a believer and this will bring
作为一个信徒，这将带来
reproach on the name of Christ you know
你知道基督的名字受到谴责
it just isn't worth it and know that you
它只是不值得，知道你
cannot get away with it that God will
无法逃脱它，上帝会
judge so in terms of this you've got to
从这个角度判断， 你必须这样做
have a plan what's the plan let me
有一个计划是什么计划让我
suggest five things these aren't in your
提出这些不属于你的五件事
notes one read proverbs once a month
注意每月一次阅读谚语
just read the proverb that it aligns
只是阅读它对齐的谚语
with the day of the month and you can
与当月的一天，你可以
read through proverbs 31 chapters you'll
通过谚语阅读31章，你会
have to double up on the February 28th
必须在2月28日加倍
and and on the other dates that don't
以及其他没有的日期
have 31 read it once a month but if
有31个月每月阅读一次，但如果
you're in this situation or if you're
你是在这种情况下，还是在你
dealing with someone who is have them
与拥有他们的人打交道
read proverbs 5 every day and then have
每天阅读谚语5然后有
them memorize you know these steps from
他们记住你知道这些步骤
this chapter so that they're focusing
本章让他们集中注意力
their mind on the truth and renewing
他们关于真相和更新的思想
their mind get them to join an
他们的心思让他们加入了
accountability group get them to plan a
问责制小组让他们计划一个
second Timothy plan that's given to you
蒂莫西的第二个计划是给你的
on the second page where they determine
在他们确定的第二页上
their areas where they need respectable
他们需要尊重的地方
distance and flight strategy and where
距离和飞行策略以及在哪里
they may need to deny any entrance for
他们可能需要 拒绝任何入口
sin and then how are they going to be
罪，然后他们将 如何
with a group or they're gonna pursue
与一群人或他们会追求
righteousness and faith and love and
正义与信仰， 爱与
peace in accountability and then I would
问责制的和平然后我会
suggest having them do a dwt sheet a
建议他们做一个dwt表a
discovering wonderful thing sheet we'll
发现奇妙的东西表我们会
talk about that tomorrow morning in the
谈到明天早上在
1st or 2nd hour that I teach I'm not
我教的第一或第二个小时我不是
sure which and we'll talk about that
确定哪个，我们会谈到这个
sheet but have them memorize the verse
表，但让他们记住这节经文
and have them pray it back to God that
并让他们向上帝祈祷
is Lord today help me to flee from any
是主今天帮助我逃离任何人
situations that promote me toward less
将我推向更少的情况
and help me live today Lord to pursue
并帮助我今天生活主追求
righteousness and faith and peace and
正义与信仰与和平与和平
love with those who call upon your name
喜欢那些呼唤你名字的人
helped me to pursue righteousness today
帮助我今天追求正义
and pursue peace and pursue love and so
追求和平，追求爱情等等
they're praying that back to God asking
他们祈祷，回神问
God to change their heart and their life
上帝改变他们的心和他们的生活
we did not get to it but it is really
我们没有达到它，但确实如此
self-explanatory John Piper came up with
不言自明的John Piper提出了这个问题
an anthem plan and you will go through
国歌的计划，你会经历
it and see how it holds very closely to
它，看看它是如何紧密相关的
what we've talked about but that plan is
我们谈过的是什么，但那个计划是
on page four of these this section of
在这部分的第4页上
your notes avoid as much as possible any
您的笔记避免尽可能任何
situation that would promote it then say
形势将促进然后说
no immediately and then turn your mind
没有立即然后转过头来
forcefully to Christ then hold the
有力地对基督然后举行
promises of the pleasure in Christ in
快感在基督的承诺
your mind and enjoy the superior
你的思想，享受优越感
satisfaction in Christ and then move to
在基督里满足，然后转向
some useful good activity you read
你读过的一些有用的好活动
through that it explains itself
通过它解释自己
you
您